Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/elyse-inferrera-89b836149 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Accounting
Event Planning
Event Management

Elyse Inferrera

Event Producer | Game Presentation | Sports Entertainment | Live Event Entertainment

Rancho Palos Verdes, California, United States

Summary

Experienced Game Entertainment Manager and Producer with a demonstrated history of working in the Sports and Entertainment Industry. Skilled in event planning, time management, event management, and Public Relations. Strong professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Business Management and Sports Management from Marymount California University.

Experience

United Football League (UFL)

UFL Game Day Entertainment and Fan Experience Consultant October 2022 - Present (2 years 5 months)

Organize, advance, and execute game days for all 8 markets in the league and produce special events beyond normal game operations: Draft, Town Halls, playoffs, and Championship. Create all game scripts in ShoFlo and create/ deliver time sheets to Broadcast, Football Ops, and league staff. Oversee the game day, operations crew, and stage managers, including scheduling, event confirmations, and payroll. Manage all sponsorship inventory and ensure accurate execution and all markets relating to videos, signage, and graphics.

Los Angeles Football Club (LAFC) Stage Manager April 2018 - Present (6 years 11 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

Organize and facilitate in-stadium production and events. Work directly with show producer to ensure pre-game and half-time events are properly executed

Outside LAFC Events:

- MLS All Star Game 2021
- CONCACAF Championship 2023
- Copa Angelina 2022 & 2023
- Leagues Cup 2023

ARTEMIS EVENTS

Associate Producer
June 2016 - Present (8 years 9 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

Organize, advance and execute various events including overseeing load in, event day, and load out

Develop budgets and account for all expenses involved with each production Create Production Timelines/ manage vendor relationships/ Liaison between client, building operations crews

Strategic planning of overall event constructs including but not limited to use of multi media elements, guest pathways and experience, timelines and execution goals, insure fundamental success of event in conjunction with client goals

Notable Events:

- Lakers Events
- Drone Racing League
- BETX

Joe Lewis Company (JLC)
Production Specialist
January 2022 - Present (3 years 2 months)
Los Angeles, California, United States

Produce and assist with various events, including but not limited to Special Olympics world games 2023, Hollywood, movie, premieres, billboard, music, award, red carpet, unified cup, Special Olympics, NFL parties, award show after parties, etc.

Angel City Football Club Stage Manager April 2022 - October 2022 (7 months)

Organize and facilitate all in Stadium production and events related to Angel city football games. Pregame celebrations, halftime, activations, post game celebrations, and sponsorship activations. I worked directly with the Show CLIer to ensure all game elements were properly executed, and that the league rules were followed in Stadium.

Entertainment Industry Response (EIR)
Covid Compliance Officer
August 2020 - May 2022 (1 year 10 months)
Los Angeles, California, United States

KCD

Producer - Gucci Space February 2022 - March 2022 (2 months)

United States

Worked directly with the Gucci Special Events and Client Advisor teams to create a unique and one of a kind Gucci Experience in Los Angeles and Dallas. Transformed an empty warehouse in the fashion district of LA and a 20,000 square-foot home in Preston Hollow into a "Gucci Space " that generated over \$14 million in sales. Arranged and managed vendors at both locations to bring to life this exclusive activation that embodied the Gucci brand. Assisted with management of budget and worked with the Gucci finance team on getting vendors on boarded.

KCD

Production Manager - LOUIS VUITTON MENS FASHION SHOW 2021 November 2021 - December 2021 (2 months)

Miami, Florida, United States

liaise with senior producer, and artistic Director to execute any production needs. Created, maintain, and updated the production schedule and worked with all vendors to ensure timely schedule. Distributed, full production, schedule and daily call sheets to all crew leads for the month of production. Supervised and provided all direction to production assistants.

Los Angeles Kings

Supervisor

November 2016 - March 2020 (3 years 5 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

- -Organize and facilitate in-arena production and events and act as a liaison between STAPLES Center and the LA Kings
- Produce and show call all games and ensure promotions are accurately executed
- Produce and direct the on-ice activities and ceremonies
- Write all game scripts in ShoFlo and create/deliver timing sheets to the National Hockey League
- Oversee and Manage the GameDay Operations Crew and Stage Managers including scheduling and event confirmations
- Manage all in-game sponsorship inventory
- Stage manage special events beyond normal game operations: Bob Miller's retirement ceremony, Festival, and Paint the Ice

- Set up activations related to fan engagement Fan Fests, Season Ticket Member Events. etc.
- Manage Events Department inventory of Gameday and event equipment including props, PA Systems, photo activations, etc.

Los Angeles Chargers Stage Manager and Production Coordinator December 2017 - December 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Greater Los Angeles Area

- Management vendors in the fan facing areas
- Coordinate special game appearances of Charger Girls and the Thunderbolts on the field
- Producer Christmas party
- Training Camp production

All Access Staging & Production Soft Good Department Manager and Inventory Tech June 2015 - April 2018 (2 years 11 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

- Manage and oversee all aspects of the Soft Goods Inventory
- Prep/receive rental orders to be used on various jobs in the entertainment industry
- Track rental inventory of all rental gear including missing and/or sold items
- Facilitate orders/requests between clients, sales representatives, and manufacturers
- Manufacture soft good with an industrial sewing machine

Freelance

Special Projects - Various June 2016 - June 2016 (1 month)

Special Olympics World Game 2023 - Berlin

- served as a producer, script, writer, stage manager, production manager, on various events and parties for the Special Olympics international (Golisano Awards, Founders Reception, Round Table, other programmed events, and Opening and Closing ceremony)

Lakers Special Events - Present

- Served as Associate Producer on various events and parties like Kobe Bryant's statue unveiling, Elgin Baylor statue, Kobe's Jersey Retirement, and Lakers Friends and Family Holiday Party BETX Experience - Production Coordinator - June 2016, 2017, 2018

- Assisted with coordination of overall event constructs and fulfillment of a dual stakeholder event. Managed load in and strike coordinated taking into consideration all vendor needs and arranged labor through the union. Acted as a liaison between BET, AEG, and Los Angeles Convention Center. managed relationships with vendors, talent, and venue for execution. Oversaw guest experience aspects of event, related to security, ingress and egress, guest flow, safety, and communications.

NBA ALL STAR GAME 2018

- Organized various aspects with the Turner Broadcasting network live events team. Managed artist green rooms. Assisted with talent movement from venue to the stage. Manage installation of the production elements related to the TBN spaces.

Education

Marymount California University
Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management,
General · (2014 - 2017)